

## Andi Muhammad Axel Reyhan Yanandhy

Student Informatics Engineering at Politeknik Negeri Jakarta / Freelance IT / Software Engineer

My name is Andi M Axel Reyhan Yanandhy,I from indonesia.I am the 1st Most Outstanding Student (Mahasiswa Berprestasi) PNJ 2021.I've served as Lead of Google Developer Student Club PNJ 2020 and vice president of English club Politeknik Negeri Jakarta 2018. I also active in other organizations such as Indonesia Linux programs, Indonesia bug hunter, Indonesian web developers,Ipv6 hurricane electric and I've filled speaker in several technology seminars in several places, I've been as a project manager at some of these projects are helping companies like PT. Galunggung Indonesia, Oriflame, PT. Abipraya and the Indonesian Ministry of Transportation website and i've been as software engineer PT.Ravelware technology.Besides that, I am the CEO of a reseller business platform,the name is Hastore.id and Founder of Xelcorp.

## Work Experience

Lead Of Google Developer Student Clubs at Google, Indonesia

Sep, 2020 - Dec, 2020

Software Engineer at PT.Ravelware Techonology, Bekasi

Aug, 2020 - Nov, 2020

Web Developer at Syahbandar (Indonesian Ministry Of

Transportation, Jakarta

Jun, 2020 - Jul, 2020

Project Manager Hardware at Abipraya, Jakarta

May, 2020 - Jun, 2020

Project Manager RFID at PT.PAM, Garut

Nov, 2019 - Dec, 2019

Web Developer at Astra, Jakarta

Sep, 2020 - Oct, 2020

Project Manager Android at Ministry of Marine Affairs and Fisheries of the Republic of Indonesia

May, 2021 - Jun, 2021

IT Development at Pelindo, Jakarta

Aug, 2021 - Oct, 2021

Education

Diploma 4 at Politeknik Negeri Jakarta, Depok

Sep, 2018 - Sep, 2022

Informatics Engineering / Computer Science

**ê** Certification

**Certificate Of Lead Google Developers** 

Sep, 2020 - Present

Certificate Of Data Analytics ASEAN

Aug, 2020 - Present

Certificate Of IPV6 Expert

Jan, 2020 - Present

**Certificate Of Android Expert** 

August, 2018 - Present

Juara 1 Mahasiswa Berprestasi Politeknik Negeri Jakarta

Jun, 2021 - Present

International LMUN in Bangkok

August, 2019

**Details** 

Kemang Ifi Graha

Bekasi, 17424

Indonesia

081213780414

axelreyhann@gmail.com

Date of birth

13 November 1999

Place of birth

Bekasi

**Nationality** 

Indonesia

**Skills** 

Web Developer

Android Developer

Design UI/UX (Adobe / Figma)

Microsoft Office

(Excel/Visio/Word/Powerpoint)

Networking

Languages

Indonesia

English

German

Arab